<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CSS3 on stephanie kim</title>
    <link>https://sdkim0739.github.io/tags/css3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CSS3 on stephanie kim</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 22:12:10 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sdkim0739.github.io/tags/css3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UChicago Ethics Bowl Website</title>
      <link>https://sdkim0739.github.io/projects/ethics-bowl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 22:12:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sdkim0739.github.io/projects/ethics-bowl/</guid>
      <description>As the only CS major amongst our Ethics Bowl crew, I&amp;rsquo;ve been summoned to create our Ethics Bowl team website.
Below is a sneak peek at the current design:
Using my own custom HTML/CSS, I&amp;rsquo;m customizing the Dopetrope template from HTML5UP to suit our design needs. The color scheme consists of mainly UChicago brand colors.
I plan to incorporate more custom JavaScript or React Native to make the landing page more dynamic, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AFROTC Detachment 195 Website Redesign</title>
      <link>https://sdkim0739.github.io/projects/det195-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 22:12:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sdkim0739.github.io/projects/det195-site/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;by &amp;ldquo;part of a development team&amp;rdquo;, I mean being one of two cadets who can edit HTML in my detachment. Hehe.
Anyways!
Since the website for our detachment is rather outdated and archived, we&amp;rsquo;re dusting it off and hoping to release a fresh website with a new design by fall of 2022.
So far, the design has been under wraps, so I don&amp;rsquo;t have any images yet! It&amp;rsquo;s going to be a classic HTML5/CSS3 framework, customizing off of an existing template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UChicago Housing Technology Summer Work</title>
      <link>https://sdkim0739.github.io/projects/housing-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 22:12:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sdkim0739.github.io/projects/housing-tech/</guid>
      <description>While I worked as a Summer Technician at UChicago Housing Technology in 2020, I created an internal metrics visualization page powered by Go to display our logs.
I wish I had code or images to link to, but unfortunately, all the work is housed internally and can&amp;rsquo;t be shared. However, I used the go-echarts plugin to make the foundation, which you can find here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EsteemBeam Mobile Application</title>
      <link>https://sdkim0739.github.io/projects/esteembeam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 22:12:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sdkim0739.github.io/projects/esteembeam/</guid>
      <description>Back when I was a wee high school sophomore in 2017, a couple of my friends and I prototyped an app at the Girls Who Code Summer Immersion Program.
And EsteemBeam was born!
EsteemBeam is an iOS/Android app that sends self-help and motivational phrases at the user&amp;rsquo;s specified frequency – daily, weekly, monthly, etc. Our target demographic was young girls, since the app&amp;rsquo;s phrases were formulated with common mental health struggles of adolescent girls in mind, such as body image or peer pressure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
